Shahdeen Z. Rahman

Student

Contact

Address

Calgary, AB, T3M 2P4

Phone

825 365 8444

E-mail

zuhaerrahman2003@gmail.c om

Skills

Customer Care

Excellent

Communication with peers

Very Good

Ability to work under pressure

Excellent

Conflict resolution

Very Good

Leadership

Very Good

Telephone etiquette

Very Good

Public speaking

Dedicated Associate with extensive experience collaborating with clients, promptly identifying needs and recommending products and services to accomplish clients' goals. Strong communicator focused on delivering outstanding customer care. Energetic worker offering outstanding telephone etiquette, social media and interpersonal skills. Well-trained individual with past experience working with children and adults. Punctual and dedicated to service with strong time management skills and ability to coordinate many scheduled activities. Excellent organizational skills and attention to detail as well as customer care and conflict resolution.

Work History

2019-03 -

Marker and assistant

2021-11

Kumon, Calgary, AB

- Marking and recording classwork and homework
- Helped students understand mathematic and reading concepts
- Supervising students over zoom calls
- Answering questions, receiving and returning emails/calls, welcoming and seating parents/students, parent/customer care
- Organizing and filing worksheets and taking inventory

2019-03 -

Volunteer

YMCA, Calgary, AB

Current

- Greeting members and verifying memberships.
- Providing identification wristbands for swimming skill level to members who may not be comfortable.
- Resolving any conflicts with facility goers.
- Supported engaging, fun and smooth-running events by helping with organization and planning.
- Freed full-time employees up for more critical work by completing clerical tasks and office work.
- Tracked volunteer hours in spreadsheets.

2017-04 -Current

Referee

CMSA (Calgary Minor Soccer Association), Calgary, AB

- Verified accuracy of score calculations before winners were announced.
- Explained and taught regulations and rules to players and coaches.
- Navigated difficult situations using effective communication and explanation of game rules.

Excellent

Recordkeeping

Very Good

Cash Registry

Average

Software

Proficiency with Microsoft
Office Apps such as Excel,
Word, and PowerPoint as
well as their Google
counterparts

Very Good

Coding Software's such as Python

Good

Languages

English

Excellent

Bengali

Excellent

French

Average

- Established clear benchmarks for performance and monitored individual and team progress, promoted good sportsmanship.
- Inspected sporting equipment for compliance with safety and event regulations.

Education

2021-09 - Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering

Current

2021-06

University of Calgary - Calgary, AB

- Dean's List 1st semester 2021
- Continuing education in Software Engineering
- Received highest rank of Alexander Rutherford Scholarship
- Received multiple government grants and funding

2018-09 - **High School Diploma**

Joane Cardinal-Schubert High School - Calgary, AB

Awarded Spirit of the Raven / Award of Excellence in:

Mathematics 20-1 AP / Physics 20 / Social 20-1 / Legal Studies
 Inter / Business Studies Intro / Sports Performance Intro / Physical
 Education 10

Member of:

 JCS Diversity Club / Model U.N. / Debate Club / Speech Club / Athletic Council / Soccer Team / Jr./Sr. Volleyball Team / Badminton Team / Track & Field Team / Cross Country Athlete

Elected to Student Rep for Principal Advisory Council from 2019-

2021

Awarded Honors Roll with Distinction

Elected Captain of Jr. Boys Volleyball

Awarded Silver Medal for Sr. Boys Volleyball

Awarded Silver Medal for Badminton Team

Certifications

| 2020-10 | YMCA Child Protection Training |
|---------|---|
| 2020-10 | WHMIS - Full Training |
| 2020-10 | Vangard Training for Volunteers & Staff |
| 2020-09 | Health, Safety & Risk Training for Volunteers |